[
  {
    "id": "562",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "EBS Snapshots are backed up to S3 in what manner?",
      "answers": [
        "Incrementally",
        "Exponentially",
        "Decreasingly",
        "EBS snapshots are not stored on S3"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Incrementally"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "563",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Do Amazon EBS volumes persist independently from the life of an Amazon EC2 instance, for example, if I terminated an EC2 instance, would that EBS volume remain?",
      "answers": [
        "yes",
        "no",
        "Only if instructed to when created",
        "Depends on the region"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["Only if instructed to when created"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "564",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Can I delete a snapshot of an EBS Volume that is used as the root device of a registered AMI?",
      "answers": [
        "yes",
        "no",
        "Only via the Command Line",
        "Only via the API"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["no"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "565",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "What must you do before you can delete a snapshot of an EBS Volume that is used as the root device of a registered AMI?",
      "answers": [
        "deregister the AMI",
        "delete the AMI",
        "you can't delete a snapshot of the root device of a registered AMI",
        "copy the AMI to another region"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["deregister the AMI"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "566",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A placement group can be deployed across multiple Availability Zones.",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "567",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "While creating the snapshots using the command line tools, which command should I be using?",
      "answers": [
        "ec2-create-snapshot",
        "ec2-fresh-snapshot",
        "ec2-deploy-snapshot",
        "ec2-new-snapshot"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["ec2-create-snapshot"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "568",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Can you attach an EBS volume to more than one EC2 instance at the same time?",
      "answers": [
        "yes",
        "no",
        "If that EC2 volume is part of an AMI",
        "Depends on the region"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["no"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "569",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "A placement group is ideal for",
      "answers": [
        "Distributing content on a CDN network",
        "EC2 instances that require high disk IO",
        "EC2 Instances that require low latency and high network throughput across multiple availability zones.",
        "EC2 instances that require high network throughput and low latency across a single availability zone."
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["EC2 instances that require high network throughput and low latency across a single availability zone."]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "570",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "Using the console, I can add a role to an EC2 instance, after that instance has been created and powered up.",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["false"]
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "571",
    "category": "Cloud Concepts",
    "info": {
      "subcategory": "EC2",
      "questionType": "multiple choice 1",
      "question": "I can change the permissions to a role, even if that role is already assigned to an existing EC2 instance, and these changes will take effect immediately.",
      "answers": [
        "true",
        "false"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": ["true"]
    }
  }
]
